-[Narrator]: In this instructional video,
you’ll learn all about the ins and outs
of what’s going to happen in the next
brand-new "Digital Circus."
-[Gangle]: [overly cheerful]
That’s right, team!
We’re working at a fast food place today.
So, roll up your sleeves
and wash your hands,
'cause we got burgers to make!
-[Jax]: Why are you talking like that?
What’s wrong with you?
-[Gangle]: Looks like somebody
doesn’t have their smile on.
Why don’t you go into the freezer
and get some patties ready?
[freezer door opens]
-[Previous Narrator]: Oh, thank God.
-[Pomni]: Yeah,
i-i-it was freezing in there.
-[Jax]: What were you --
Who is th--
What’s going on???
-[Gangle]: Find out in the brand new episode
coming atcha soon!!!
-[Narrator]: And then, nobody was
teleported anywhere ever again,
and there was everlasting peace.